(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T20:13:55.762127",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Let me show you
OK?
真々独壇場
A striking, one-man show,
列車列車
full speed ahead.
ギミギミナイト
Gimme gimme night,
夜々々々 証拠だんぜん
night after night, undeniable proof.
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass is a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no
Come on, say no,
低音響かせろ
now let's bring the bass.
なんだかなって つまんないこともあるでしょう
Things tend to get boring sometimes.
ロンリー論理のノート ハンディ本気脱走
Lonely logic note, handy serious escape.
やんなっちまった泥に bad ご法度だろうが
Can't take this anymore, it's bad taboo,
浸れて堕ちて そろそろいっか
drown and drop in, it's about time.
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
Let's work harder until I get excited!
繋がろうひとりよりふたり 増えたら安心 心配ないや
Let's connect, two is better than one.
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright, let me do it, don't mind.
波あり難題 みんなで乗りかかっちゃえば案外さくっと行っていそう♪
If we all ride the waves, it's a breeze!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass is a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show.
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no
Come on, say no,
低音響かせろ
now let's bring the bass.
今宵は暗転パーティー
Yeah, tonight's a party in the dark!
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness!
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
ここらでバイバイ let go
it's time to say bye-bye, let go.
どんな劣等感だてて 即興の血小板で
Any complex, with a freestyle platelet,
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
shove it, take it away, aye!
Up and down なテンション ねぇまいっちんぐっていの相当
Pumped up and down, pretty stressed out,
ドバっと噴き出すのは 本音の独り言
spit it out at once!
「別に興味ない」
"Not really interested."
「特に関係ない」
"Don't care."
合図を奏でて PrrPrrPrr yeah
Send signal (Prr, prr, prr, prr, yeah)!
ほら集まって夜行だ 音鳴っていこう
Let's come together, live the night!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass is a K.O.
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness!
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
今宵も暗転パーティーだ
tonight's a party in the dark.
Woah またのお越しを きっと
We look forward to serving you again!
Woah 次回までお元気で
Please take care until next time,
ここらでバイバイ let go
it's time to say bye-bye, let go.
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness!
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
ここらでバイバイ let go
it's time to say bye-bye, let go.
どんな劣等感だてて 即興の血小板で
Any complex, with a freestyle platelet,
抑え込んで 突っ込んで 仕舞い込んじゃうでしょ
shove it, take it away, aye!
恋の butterfly
Koi no butterfly...
noise scape
Noisescape.
ロンリー論理のノート
Lonely logic note,
ハンディ本気脱走
handy serious escape.
やんなっちまった泥に
Can't take this anymore,
浸れて堕ちて そろそろいっか
drown and drop in, it's about time.
もっと頑張って アガるまでもっと頑張って
Let's work harder until I get excited!
繋がろうひとりよりふたり 増えたら安心 心配ないや
Let's connect, two is better than one.
Alright 任せて don't mind
Alright, let me do it, don't mind.
波あり難題 みんなで乗りかかっちゃえば案外さくっと行っていそう♪
If we all ride the waves, it's a breeze!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass is a K.O.
ふわふわしたいならどうぞ
So be it, if you're light-hearted
開演準備しちゃおうか
Let's get ready for the show.
泣いてても笑ってても愛してね
Cry or laugh, just love me okay?
ほら say no
Come on, say no,
低音響かせろ
now let's bring the bass.
今宵は暗転パーティー
Yeah, tonight's a party in the dark!
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness!
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
ここらでバイバイ let go
it's time to say bye-bye, let go.
騒ぎ起こすためにステイ
Raise your voice to save the day,
一切合切忘れてシャララオシャララオ
forgetting all the pain, let go!
合図を鳴らせば
Send signal!
ほら集まって夜行だ 音鳴っていこう
Let's come together, live the night!
半端なら K.O.
Half-ass is a K.O.
Woah 踊りだせ 踊りだせ 孤独は殺菌 満員御礼
Dance, dance, sanitize loneliness!
Woah 痛みまで おシェアで
Even the pain, let's share it,
ここらでバイバイ let go
it's time to say bye-bye, let go.
Your action and your words were never match
You're such a piece of trash and that's a fact
You made me feel that I'm not good enough
I gave you my best, but you're not impressed
Who's Toxic ? It's You !
Who's toxic? It's you!
It falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out
I am begging no more
It's you the one who tried to make me go insane
It's you who should stop and feel ashamed
I think you're lame, it's all in vain
I better just ignore it anyway
It's you the one who turn my world upside down
It's you who break the rules and pull me under the bus
Please go away 'Cause you can't stay
Just go to hell
Now tell me why
You make me question my reality
you made me question my reality?
Now I have the lesson learned
This is all I need to know
It's you the one who make me feel that I am weak
Your words hit so hard, made me black and blue
I know the truth But you deny
Who cares about it anyway ?
who cares about it anyway?
Who's Toxic ? It's You !
Who's toxic? It's you!
It's you the one who spread the lies, but then you fled
It's you the one who deceit and never regret
I have to warn ya You know there's karma
I need no drama
So, who's toxic ? It's you !
So, who's toxic? It's you!
It falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out
I am begging no more
It's you the one who try to make me go insane
It's you who should stop and feel ashamed
I think you're lame, it's all in vain
I better just ignore it anyway
It's you the one who turn my world upside down
It's you who break the rules and pull me under the bus
Please go away 'Cause you can't stay
Just go to hell
Now tell me why
You make me question my reality
you made me question my reality?
Now I have the lesson learned
This is all I need to know
Your action and your words were never match
You're such a piece of trash and that's a fact
You made me feel that I'm not good enough
I gave you my best, but you're not impressed
It falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out, I am begging no more
It's you, the one who spread the words that I am fake
It's you, the one who stabbed me right in the back
And now you say that I misread
But I don't even really care anyway
It's you, who twist on things, but then I took the blame
It's you, who messed around and do all hits and runs
You made my days a living hell, now I don't care
Who's toxic? It's you!
Can't hear ya, can't hear ya, can't hear ya
It's bullshit, it's bullshit, it's bullshit
It falls apart, you broke my heart
You're spreading more lies and lies and lies
I had enough, cut it out, I am begging no more
It's you, the one who tried to make me go insane
It's you, who should stop and feel ashamed
I think you're lame, it's all in vain
I better just ignore it anyway
It's you, the one who turned my world upside down
It's you, who break the rules and pulled me under the bus
Please go away, 'cause you can't stay
Just go to hell
Now tell me why
You made me question my reality
Now I have the lesson learned
This is all I need to know
Guys!
Kalian udah guess— Kalian udah guess, akhirnya, akhirnya
You guys guessed— You guessed it, finally, finally
kita melakukan 3D live lagi, setelah menunggu beberapa tahun lamanya.
we're doing a 3D live again, after waiting for several years.
Buat kalian yang ingin ikut me-hype stream ini, kalian bisa pakai hashtag #EclipseBreaker3DLive.
For those of you who want to help hype this stream, you can use the hashtag #EclipseBreaker3DLive.
Sebelum itu, Muna mau kenalin nih, guys. Kalau misalnya kalian liat nih, di belakangnya Muna ya, tuh.
Before that, Muna wants to introduce this, guys. If you guys look, behind Muna, yeah, look.
Se-cute bagus banget ya, guys! Apalagi nih, Muna paling suka monitornya, guys. Soalnya monitornya itu, guys, uh! Bulan banget!
It's so cute and looks so good, guys! Especially this, Muna likes the monitor the most, guys. Because the monitor, guys, wow! So moon-like!
Everything in here is Muna, Hoshinova, Ko-de. Belum main nih, guys. Belum main nih. Kalau misalnya kalian liat ya, guys, di belakangnya Muna ya, guys.
Everything in here is Muna Hoshinova's code. We haven't played yet, guys. Not yet. If you guys look, yeah, guys, behind Muna, yeah, guys.
We have... Muna Peter! Ya, they, they're kind of, kind of shy right now, so they didn't, didn't move anything.
We have... Muna Peter! Yeah, they, they're kind of, kind of shy right now, so they didn't, didn't move anything.
Gimana? Kalian suka enggak sama nyanyiannya Muna? Semoga kalian suka ya.
How is it? Do you guys like Muna's singing? I hope you guys like it.
Karena ya, sebenarnya cukup capek ya Muna loncat-loncat dari tadi.
Because, well, it's actually quite tiring jumping around since earlier.
Tapi kita masih ada lagu lagi nih buat kalian. Sebelum kita pindah ke lagu selanjutnya, Muna ganti baju dulu ya.
But we still have another song for you guys. Before we move on to the next song, Muna's gonna change clothes first.
Tunggu sebentar ya.
Wait a moment, yeah.
Gimana? Uwoh, u-wow, u-wow, gimana? Fotonya bagus banget ya, guys! Eclipse Breaker!
How is it? Wow, wow, wow, how is it? The photos look so good, guys! Eclipse Breaker!
Di lagu kali ini, Muna akan menyanyi lagu-lagu yang agak, agak, agak nge-band dikit, guys. Soalnya kita konsepnya itu ala-ala band gitu, biar live-nya berasa banget.
In this song, Muna will sing songs that are a bit, bit, bit band-like, guys. Because our concept is like a band style, so the live feels real.
Jadi, kita akan mulai dengan... I got Deja Vu! We're gonna start with Deja Vu. I hope you guys are ready.
So, we will start with... I got Deja Vu! We're gonna start with Deja Vu. I hope you guys are ready.
I got deja vu
It’s been many years and I’m thinking
How I ever thought we should be together
In the beginning it was sweet but it’s a shame
How quickly it turned all sour
You let a good thing slip away
I waited for hours
You would leave me on read
While you laid on her bed
I know that we were never meant to be but oh
I got deja vu
Me & you never got to finish what we started
How you always wanted somebody new
Had me broken hearted
But I realized you were no good
Now when I look back I laugh about it
I’m so glad that we are through
When I get deja vu
i got déjà vu
it 's been many years and i 'm thinking
It's been many years and I'm thinking,
how i ever thought we should be together
in the beginning it was sweet but it 's a shame how quickly it turned all sour
In the beginning it was sweet, but it's a shame how quickly it turned all sour.
you let a good thing slip away
i waited for hours
you would leave me on read
while you laid on her bed
i know that we were never meant to be but oh
i got déjà vu
me & you never got to finished what we started
Me and you never got to finish what we started.
how you always wanted somebody new had me broken hearted
How you always wanted somebody new, had me broken-hearted.
but i realized you were no good now when i look back i laugh about it
i 'm so glad that we are through
I'm so glad that we are through,
when i get déjà vu
you said you 're crazy about me that i had your full attention
You said you're crazy about me, that I had your full attention,
but i wasn't the only one guess you just forgot to mention
i 'm so over it thank god i dodged a bullet
I'm so over it, thank God I dodged a bullet.
made so many mistakes but they made me who i am
i 'm alright 'cause now i know better better oh
I'm alright 'cause now I know better, better, oh!
i got déjà vu me & you never got to finished what we started
I got déjà vu! Me and you never got to finish what we started.
how you always wanted somebody new had me broken hearted
How you always wanted somebody new, had me broken-hearted.
but i realized you were no good now when i look back i laugh about it
i 'm so glad that we are through
I'm so glad that we are through,
when i get déjà vu
nothing will stay the same and though you played your game
i have no complaints because it made me who i am
looking back i smile can't believe how far i 've come
Looking back I smile, can't believe how far I've come.
what was i thinking ? it got me singing
What was I thinking? It got me singing!
i got déjà vu
me & you never got to finished what we started
Me and you never got to finish what we started.
how you always wanted somebody new had me broken hearted
How you always wanted somebody new, had me broken-hearted.
but i realized you were no good now when i look back i laugh about it
i 'm so glad that we are through
I'm so glad that we are through,
when i get déjà vu
i 'm so glad we 're through when i get déjà vu
I'm so glad we're through when I get déjà vu.
High Tide
[Title: High Tide]
when you look up at the night sky what do you see ?
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see?
the glowing beauty in the twilight it 's no mystery
The glowing beauty in the twilight, it's no mystery.
now watch me set the scene , i 'll light it all up
Now watch me set the scene, I'll light it all up.
when the time has come , i 'll be rising high
When the time has come, I'll be rising high.
longing for me like a lifeline whenever you see my shine i 'll catch your eye
Longing for me like a lifeline, whenever you see my shine I'll catch your eye.
it 's pulling you in like gravity you will be bowing on your knees , yeah
It's pulling you in like gravity, you will be bowing on your knees, yeah.
pulling you in , close to me watch my glory and might following me like a high tide
Pulling you in, close to me, watch my glory and might, following me like a high tide.
my reign will never stop the tide begins to rise up to the top
let my power ignite following me like a high tide
woah , oh
Woah, oh.
i can be a bright enigma it 's no surprise
I can be a bright enigma, it's no surprise.
but you'll give in to the brilliance like a moth to a light
playing hard to get , but i ain't patient you'll succumb to my blinding radiance , yeah
Playing hard to get, but I ain't patient, you'll succumb to my blinding radiance, yeah.
when you look up at the night sky what do you see ? my shine an effulgent sight
When you look up at the night sky, what do you see? My shine, an effulgent sight.
it 's pulling you in like gravity you will be bowing on your knees , yeah
It's pulling you in like gravity, you will be bowing on your knees, yeah.
pulling you in , close to me watch my glory and might following me like a high tide
Pulling you in, close to me, watch my glory and might, following me like a high tide.
my reign will never stop the tide begins to rise up to the top
let my power ignite following me like a high tide
following me like a high tide woah , oh
Following me like a high tide, woah, oh.
i shine the brightest in the night the way the waves come nigh , oh , ah yeah
I shine the brightest in the night, the way the waves come nigh, oh, ah yeah.
it 's pulling you in like gravity you will be bowing on your knees , yeah
It's pulling you in like gravity, you will be bowing on your knees, yeah.
pulling you in , close to me watch my glory and might following me like a high tide
Pulling you in, close to me, watch my glory and might, following me like a high tide.
my reigns will never stop the tide begins to rise up to the top
My reign will never stop, the tide begins to rise up to the top.
let my power ignite following me like a high tide
follow me , follow me , follow me woah , oh
Follow me, follow me, follow me, woah, oh.
following me like a high tide follow me , follow me , follow me
Following me like a high tide, follow me, follow me, follow me.
woah , oh yeah
Woah, oh yeah.
Perisai Jitu
[Title: Perisai Jitu]
warna cerah yang terlihat diriku mahir sembunyi rasa
These visible bright colors formed by my well-concealed feelings.
sebenarnya hitam pekat kututup rapat , jadi rahasia
In reality, they are all pitch black, I sealed them as a secret.
satu dua kali , ' ku tak apa - apa kamu pikir hidupku baik - baik saja ?
Once or twice, I can accept, but did you think my life is all okay?
Satu dua kali, ku tak apa-apa
One or two times, I'm just fine,
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is going just fine.
Siapa yang peduli ku punya air mata?
Who cares if I have tears in my eyes?
Kamu hanya minta diri diberikan tawa
You only ask to be given laughter.
Satu dua kali, ku tak apa-apa
One or two times, I'm just fine,
Tapi sampai kapan pun begitu
But however long it goes like that,
Malam hari berwahana
At night, taking a ride
Pikiran liar, ku juaranya
Wild thoughts, I'm the champion at it.
Bukan ku tak berusaha
It's not that I'm not trying,
Ingin ku lepas sekuat tenaga
I want to let go with all my might.
Satu dua kali, ku tak apa-apa
One or two times, I'm just fine,
Kamu pikir hidupku baik-baik saja
You think my life is going just fine.
Siapa yang peduli ku punya air mata?
Who cares if I have tears in my eyes?
Kamu hanya minta diri diberikan tawa
You only ask to be given laughter.
Satu dua kali, ku tak apa-apa
One or two times, I'm just fine,
Tapi sampai kapan pun begitu
But however long it goes like that,
Taut Hati...
Bound hearts...
Tapi kau pasti yang ku percaya
But you're definitely the one I trust,
Tempat berbagi cerita
A place to share stories,
Tangis pilu, tawa gembira
Sorrowful tears, joyful laughter.
Takjub bagaimana kita saling mengerti tanpa ada kata-kata
Amazed at how we understand each other without any words.
Kita bisa selalu saling menjaga
We can always take care of each other.
Kepak sayapku jauh tanpa takut ku kan terjatuh
My wings flap far without fear of falling down.
Jika lelah aku tau dirimu tempat ku berteduh
If I'm tired, I know you're the place where I take shelter.
Senangmu bahagiaku, kesalmupastilah sedihku
Your joy is my happiness, your annoyance is surely my sadness.
Walau kita jarang temu, kita selalu bisa saling bertumpu
Even though we rarely meet, we can always lean on each other.
Walau kita seperti air dan api, tapi kita selalu bisa saling mengerti
Even though we are like water and fire, we can always understand each other.
Bisa saling bertumpu...
Able to lean on each other...
身も心も…
My body and soul...
この手で make you mine
With these hands, I'll make you mine.
Wow wow wow...
Oh baby, i need you, i need you ずっと…
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
君を視るたび上書きされてく欲求に
Every time I see you, desire rewrites itself,
重なる eyes, eyes, eyes
Eyes, eyes, eyes colliding,
胸打つ your smile, smile, smile
Your smile, smile, smile strikes my heart.
ねえその姿形が拍車掛けてく
Hey, that figure, that shape, everything's driving me wild.
恋から愛、愛、愛
From a crush into love, love, love,
毎秒おかしくなってく
Every second, I'm losing my mind.
手を伸ばせばもう届く距離 危険な “a to z” 試したい
If I reach out, it's close enough. A dangerous "A to Z", let's try it out.
穏やかに恋したい どんなシーンも私に見せて
I wanna love you gently. Show me any scene, let me see it all.
このまま stay by my side
Stay by my side, just like this.
“どこにも行かないで”
"Don't go anywhere."
aww! 100% 純粋な愛だから ねえ、いいでしょう？
Aww! 100% pure love, that's for sure. Come on, isn't it okay?
止められない感情 その腕で抱き締めてよ
These feelings, I can't hold back. Wrap me up tight in your arms.
aww! 遠くからじゃ嫌 もっともっと近くで認め合いたい
Boy, I wanna touch your love. No more distance, no way, I need you closer, every day.
暴れ狂う衝動 持て余すだけならツライ hey me! what’s wrong with me?
Let's be real, no more lies. Wild emotions running free, if I can't control it, it's too much for me. Hey, me! What's wrong with me?
何も問題ない 普通だし (my name) 君の全部知りたい
Nothing's wrong, just me being me. I wanna know all about you.
i do need you 今すぐ
I do need you, right now.
最初は “声を聴く” それだけでよかった
At first, just hearing your voice was enough.
身も心も… この手で make you mine
Body and soul... With this hand, make you mine
wow wow wow (yeah) oh baby, i need you, i need you ずっと…
Wow wow wow (yeah) Oh baby, I need you, I need you always...
君を視るたび上書きされてく欲求に
When you smile at someone else
重なりeyes, eyes, eyes 胸打つyour smile, smile, smile
It frustrates me, I can't hide it
ねぇその姿形総てが引っ掛けかけてく
I realized it was me
恋から愛、愛、愛 毎秒おかしくなってく
I wanna keep you all to myself
手を伸ばせばもう届く距離 危険な“a to z”試したい
Maybe I should chain you up
穏やかに恋したい どんなシーンも私に魅せて
In a room just for us, so close
このままstay by my side “どこにも行かないで”
I wanna watch everything you do and say
aww! 100%純粋な愛だから ねぇ、いいでしょう？
I wanna sleep with my cheek next to yours, let me feel your breath on me
止められない感情その腕で抱き締めてよ
Stay by your side, forevermore
(boy, i wanna touch your love) aww! 遠くからじゃ嫌
I won't let you go anywhere
ずっともっと近くで認め合いたい 暴れ狂う衝動持て余すならツライ
100% depend on me, that's all, come on, isn't it okay?
hey me ! what’s wrong with me ? ( say ) 何も問題ない普通だし (my name)
Love and hate turning black, take it all in, don't hold back
君の全部知りたい i do need you 今すぐ
Is something wrong with me? Even if it is, there's no turning back
最初は“声を聴く”それだけでよかった だけど次第にwhy? 我が儘になった
Wild emotions running free, no stopping me, no way
誰かに笑いかけるその仕草に 嫉妬隠せない自分に気付いた
Hey! me! What's wrong with me? Nothing's wrong, just me being me (my name)
「独り占めにしたい」いっそ、鎖に繋いで 二人だけの部屋至近距離 (go)
I wanna know all about you, I do need you, right now
行動発言監視したい 頬を寄せて眠りたいその吐息感じさせて
When I close my eyes, it's endless
永遠にstay by your side “どこにも行かせない”
I want to experience love, my way
aww! 100%私だけに依存して
Boy, you...
ねぇ、いいでしょう？ 黒く染まる愛憎まるごと受け入れてよ
Mine... all mine...
(boy, i wanna touch your love) aww! 私、変かしら？
Stay by my side, just like this, don't ever leave me
だとしても引き返せない歪んでくworld 暴れ狂う衝動歯止め効かせない絶対
100% pure love, that's for sure, come on, isn't it okay?
hey me ! what’s wrong with me ? ( say ) 何も問題ない普通だし (my name)
These feelings, I can't hold back, wrap me up tight in your arms
君の全部知りたい i do need you 今すぐ 目目を閉じればとめどない恋愛観触れたいの
No more distance, no way, I need you closer, every day
boy, you 私の… 私だけの… このままstay by my side
Wild emotions running free, if I can't control it, it's too much for me
“二度と離れないで” aww! 100%純粋な愛だから
Hey! me! What's wrong with me? Nothing's wrong, just me being me (my name)
ねぇ、いいでしょう？ 止められない感情その腕で抱き締めてよ
I wanna know all about you, I do need you, right now
(boy, i wanna touch your love) aww! 遠くからじゃ嫌 ずっともっと近くで認め合いたい
Wow wow wow...
暴れ狂う衝動持て余すならツライ
Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
hey me ! what’s wrong with me ? ( say ) 何も問題ない普通だし (my name)
Wow wow wow... Oh baby, I need you, I need you forever...
君の全部知りたい i do need you 今すぐ
(Music playing / pose)
Woah, Nerissa!
I can't believe our plan to make a song together came true!
I know!
Ahaha!
Thank you so much!
I can't believe that I get to sing with you, the Moona Hoshinova!
It's such a dream come true!
Oh my god, me too!
So, this song's actually about two girls who falling in love with one person and wanted to become their lover.
So, this song's actually about two girls who're falling in love with one person and wanted to become their lover.
Um, this is actually not talking about a good romance, everyone. So, it's more like some and other toxic relationships who want to be love 100% right, Nerissa? Right. Uh, you know, we all probably have some experiences with toxic love.
Um, this is actually not talking about a good romance, everyone. So, it's more like some other toxic relationship who wants to be loved 100% right, Nerissa?
But, uh, Moona, I have to tell you, when I was recording this, I was actually thinking about you.
He?
Oh!
You love it 100%?
Mhm, I do. 100%.
Nice. Anyway, thank you so much, Nerissa, for accepting my offer to do it with me.
Oh my god, I love your voice so much!
Ah, thank you. Ah, that means so much to me because I love your voice so much!
Thank you for inviting me, and also, happy birthday! I hope this next year of your life is even better than the last.
Aw, thank you!
Ah, thank you! And also, thank you everyone!
All right, after this, there will be another member to join to sing with me.
So, are you guys ready? Now, let's move to the next song!
Yay! Yay!
Maze Town
突き刺び闇を睨む今宵も
Piercing the darkness, glaring at the night once more
交差点の真ん中 急ぐ人に紛れて
amidst the bustling crowd,
僕だけがあてもなく 漂うみたいだ
I drift alone without a clue.
流行りの歌は いつも
The popular songs are always...
僕は歌ってない
I never sing them.
ねえビジョンの中 から
Hey, from inside the vision,
笑いかけないでで
don't smile at me like that.
また今日も声にならずに 飲み込んだ感情
Once again, emotions swallowed without a voice today.
下書き埋め尽くして
Filling up the rough drafts,
ああ そうやって何千回夜を超える
Ah, crossing the night thousands of times like that—
僕のため それだけ それだけだったんだよ
for my sake, that was all, that was all it was.
出口探し 溢れただけの言葉
Searching for an exit, just overflowing words.
君の心へ届いて 隙間をちょっと埋めるなら
Reaching your heart, if it fills the gap just a little bit,
こんな僕でも ここにいる 叫ぶよ
Even a clumsy me is right here—I'll shout it out!
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
問われることは何故か 将来のことばかり
Why do people always ask about the future?
華やかに馴染まない この心を無視して
Ignoring this heart that doesn't fit in with glamour,
輝かしい明日に 推奨しないでくれ
Don't push a shining tomorrow on me.
夜空にチカチカ光る 頼りない星屑
Twinkling faintly in the night sky, unreliable stardust.
躊躇いながらはぐれて
Hanging my head, I stagger along.
ああ 彷徨っている それが僕
Ah, wandering around—that's just who I am,
僕になる それしか それしかできないんだろう
I can only be myself, that's all I can do.
誰の真似も上手くできないんだ
I can't imitate anyone else well.
こんな痛い日々をなんで 退屈だって片付ける?
Why write off such painful days as boring?
よろめきながらでも もがいているんだよ
Even while hesitating, I'm yearning for something.
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
僕のため それだけ それだけだったんだよ
For my sake, that was all, that was all it was.
涙流し やっと生まれた言葉
Shedding tears, words finally born.
どこかで同じように ヒリヒリする胸抱えて
Somewhere just like this, holding a throbbing chest,
震える君に 僕もいる 叫ぶよ
To you who are trembling, I'm here too—I'll shout it out!
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
交差点の真ん中 急ぐ人に紛れて
Intersection in the middle, running through hurriedly.
僕だけがあてもなく 漂うみたいだ
Drifting alone, clueless.
流行りの歌は いつも 僕は歌ってない
Popular songs, I never sing them.
ねえ ビジョンの中から 笑いかけないで
Hey, from inside the vision, don't smile at me.
また今日も声にならずに 飲み込んだ感情
Swallowed emotions today too without a voice.
下書き埋め尽くして ああ そうやって何千回夜を超えて
Filling up the drafts, ah, crossing the night thousands of times,
僕のため それだけ それだけだったんだよ
For my sake, that was all, that was all it was.
出口探し 溢れただけの言葉
Searching for an exit, overflowing words.
君の心へ届いて 隙間をちょっと埋めるなら
Reaching your heart, filling the gap just a little,
こんな僕でも ここにいる 叫ぶよ
Even a clumsy me is right here—I'll shout it out!
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
問われることは何故か 将来のことばかり
Why do people always ask about the future?
華やかに馴染まない この心を無視して
Ignoring this heart that doesn't fit in with glamour,
輝かしい明日に 推奨しないでくれ
Don't push a shining tomorrow on me.
夜空にチカチカ光る 頼りない星屑
Twinkling faintly in the night sky, unreliable stardust.
躊躇いながらはぐれて
Hanging my head, I stagger along.
ああ 彷徨っている それが僕
Ah, wandering around—that's just who I am,
僕になる それしか それしかできないんだろう
I can only be myself, that's all I can do.
誰の真似も上手くできないんだ
I can't imitate anyone else well.
こんな痛い日々をなんで 退屈だって片付ける?
Why write off such painful days as boring?
よろめきながらでも もがいているんだよ
Even while hesitating, I'm yearning for something.
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
僕のため それだけ それだけだったんだよ
For my sake, that was all, that was all it was.
涙流し やっと生まれた言葉
Shedding tears, words finally born.
どこかで同じように ヒリヒリする胸抱えて
Somewhere just like this, holding a throbbing chest,
震える君に 僕もいる 叫ぶよ
To you who are trembling, I'm here too—I'll shout it out!
迷い星のうた
The Stray Star's Song.
癖になっちゃった
It's become a habit,
ママ 悪い子になっちゃったけど
Mom, I turned into a bad kid.
癖になっちゃったなら仕方がないでしょっ
If it's become a habit, I guess it can't be helped, right?
君に病み付いちゃった
You've been infected with me.
言わない 言えない 禁断症状
Forbidden symptom, won't say it, can't say it.
言わない 言えない 手遅れになっちゃった
Won't say it, can't say it, it's already too late.
「可愛い、何しても可愛い」
"Cute, cute no matter what you do,"
「可愛い、何したっていいよ」
"Cute, whatever you do is fine,"
「可愛い、何しても可愛い」
"Cute, cute no matter what you do,"
だったら「離れたい」ってことも 許してくれるよね?
If that's the case, can you forgive me even if I say "I want to leave"?
癖になっちゃった
It's become a habit,
ママ 悪い子になっちゃったけどさ
Mom, I turned into a bad kid, but...
癖になっちゃったなら仕方がないでしょ
If it's become a habit, I guess it can't be helped.
だって私 正しく生きてきた処女
After all, I'm a virgin who has lived righteously.
おのれ よくも私を
Oh my, how dare you treat me like this—
どんな形でも受け入れる奴隷
accepting me in any form like a slave,
奴隷みたいなの
just like a slave.
癖になっちゃった
It's become a habit...
ママ 悪い子になっちゃったけどさ
Mom, I turned into a bad kid, but...
癖になっちゃったなら仕方がないでしょっ
If it's become a habit, I guess it can't be helped, right?
君に病み付いた
I've been infected with you.
愛も哀も余さずちょうだい
Give me all your love and sorrow,
厭くまで情に縺り込めて
twisting it into passion until you're sick of it.
I could die
ほら頽る双眸
look at those collapsing eyes,
脳に咲いた少女地獄
a girl's hell blooming in the brain.
I know 相変わらず迷妄
I know, delusion as usual,
あれこれ欠けて蠢かれて
this and that missing and writhing around.
人間然としたその表情
That suspiciously human-like expression—
もう一切 禍穢と焚べる
let's burn everything away as impurities.
初めましてのキスを
Our first kiss—
しましょう
let's do it.
何も考えないで
Without thinking about anything,
なんだか不満 私のロッジは
somehow dissatisfied, my lodge is...
まるで運命な異端を
Like a fateful heresy,
結び付ける お遊び
binding it together as a game.
簡単だ 騙されて織りこ ほらトリコ
Easy to be fooled and woven into a trap, look, your captive!
ねぇ あなたの逃げ場は私
Hey, your only place to run is me,
魅力が引き寄せる
my charm draws you in.
あの世にあなた
To the other world, you...
居場所はない ならば仕方がない
Have no place to belong, so it can't be helped.
朽ちるまで光りましょう
Let's shine until we decay.
あなたの居場所は私
Your place to belong is me.
あの子にあなたへの愛はない
That girl has no love for you,
ならば仕方がない
so it can't be helped.
私たちちぎりましょう
Let's make our pact.
明かしましょう
Let's reveal it.
ねぇ あなたの逃げ場は私
Hey, your only place to run is me,
魅力が引き寄せる
my charm draws you in.
あの世にあなたの居場所はない ならば仕方がない
You have no place in the other world, so it can't be helped.
朽ちるまで光りましょう
Let's shine until we decay.
窓の外からそっと
Gently from outside the window,
教えてくれたのね
you taught me, didn't you?
出逢いの時を
The moment of our encounter—
あなたが弾くピアノは
the piano you play
紫陽花に軽く歌い
sings lightly to the hydrangeas.
立ち止まる 私にもボロと
Stopping in my tracks, even to me...
振る舞い速く 戻れるの?
Acting fast, can I go back?
今なら大丈夫さ
Now it'll be alright.
嘘は言わないで 噂のひと
Don't lie to me, person of rumors.
ノンノン ドキドキ響いているのよ
Non-non (thumping) it's echoing!
ギュンギュン ギュッあの日からだと大嫌いよ うそつき
Gyun-gyun (squeeze) since that day I hate you, liar!
ねぇアジサイ 私だけ
Hey hydrangeas, only me
はら はら はら なぐさめて
flutter, flutter, flutter, comfort me.
帰れるの?
Can I go back?
気にしないでいいよさあ
Don't worry about it, now then!
曖昧な優しさに苦しかったら
If ambiguous kindness was painful,
戻りたくないの
I don't want to go back.
ギュンギュン穴埋めのメロディ
Gyun-gyun melody filling the gaps,
だめ だめ やっぱ やっぱ 恋はメリーゴーランド
no no, as expected, love is a merry-go-round!
大切に少しだけ
Cherish it just a little,
春と夏の真中
right in the middle of spring and summer.
あの子と同じように
Just like that girl,
連れ去られちゃった
I was carried away.
無邪気にしゃしゃり出て
Innocently pushing in,
つま先が彷徨うのよ
my toes are wandering around.
ねぇアジサイ 私だけ
Hey hydrangeas, only me
慰めて
comfort me.
帰れるの?
Can I go back?
良いにしなくていい
It's fine not to mind.
曖昧な優しさに苦しんだら
If you suffered from ambiguous kindness,
泣きたくなる
you'll want to cry.
なんの聞きたくないの
I don't want to hear anything,
ギュンギュン穴埋めのメロディ
gyun-gyun melody filling the gaps.
だめ だめ やっぱ やっぱ
No no, as expected,
今度はどの子?
which girl is it this time?
やんやん魔性少女でも
Even if it's a demonic girl,
男性許してしまおう
let's forgive him completely.
だて だて だて だて ドキドキ
Just pretending, pounding heart—
エチュードは1曲だけ
just one etude.
カーテン揺らす風が 窓の外から そっと
A breeze rustling the curtains softly from outside the window
教えてくれたのね
told me...
出逢いの時を
the time we met.
あなたが弾くピアノは 紫陽花に軽く歌い
The piano you play softly sings to the hydrangeas,
立ち止まるわたしにも ポロンポロンふりそそぐ
showering down on me as I stop in my tracks.
「戻れるの？」
"Can I go back?"
「今なら大丈夫さ…。」
"If it's now, it'll be fine..."
ウソは言わないで！
Don't tell lies!
ウワサの人
You rumored person,
ノンノン響いているのよ
non-stop, it echoes through
ギュンギュンピュアなハートに ダメダメまだダメ
my pounding, pure heart—no, no, not yet!
流し目だけは
Only a sidelong glance,
いやんいやんあなたの指が
no, no, as your fingers
だんだん激しく動き
move increasingly intensely,
ときどきドキドキ
throbbing with excitement—
いたずらなエチュード
a mischievous etude.
いやいやもういや いたずらなエチュード
No, no, no more, a mischievous etude!
Yaa, semuanya!
Yay, everyone!
Itulah lagu-lagu kita hari ini, kila.
Those were our songs for today!
Wow, banyak banget ya!
Wow, there are so many, right!
Lagunya hari ini, kita semua beneran full nyanyi, guys.
Today's songs, we all really sang our hearts out, guys.
Aku, aduh, huh...
I... oh man, phew...
Ngomong-ngomong ya, tentang lagu-lagu yang udah kita nyanyiin sama teman-teman, member-member Hololive.
Speaking of the songs we sang together with friends, the Hololive members,
Ah, terima kasih semuanya!
ah, thank you everyone!
Semoga kalian semua suka, dan semoga semuanya menyenangkan.
Hope you all like it, and hope it was all enjoyable.
Ya, capek banget, guys.
Man, I'm so tired, guys.
Soalnya ya, persiapan untuk 3D ini tuh, wow, panjang banget.
Because, you know, preparation for this 3D was, wow, so long.
Soalnya ini kan, untuk birthday ya, kita kita sudah bersama kurang lebih hampir 5 tahun.
Because this is for my birthday, we've been together for almost 5 years.
Jadi, Moona mau bilang terima kasih semuanya telah mendukung Moona.
So, Moona wants to say thank you to everyone for supporting Moona.
Dan juga semoga kalian tertarik...
And also hopefully you're interested...
untuk membeli merch-nya, Moona Hoshinova!
in buying the merch, Moona Hoshinova!
Selamat datang semuanya yang telah datang dan menonton Moona Hoshinova. Ini merupakan Birthday Commemorative Full Set...
Welcome everyone who has come and watched Moona Hoshinova. This is the Birthday Commemorative Full Set...
...yang diisikan oleh MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat
...filled with the MoonRadiance Wide Rubber Mat
yang diilustrasikan oleh Nyori Mama. Terima kasih, I love you so much!
illustrated by Nyori Mama. Thank you, I love you so much!
Terus kita juga ada MoonRockMelody Plushie Keychain. Kamu lagi nih punya plushie Moona Hoshinova yang versi rock, guys!
Next, we also have the MoonRockMelody Plushie Keychain. You guys also get Moona Hoshinova's plushie in a rock version, guys!
Dan selanjutnya kita ada MoonAMP Shoulder Bag. Ini tas slempang, kalian bisa taruh HP dan dompet kalian!
And next we have the MoonAMP Shoulder Bag. A sling bag where you can put your phone and wallet!
Terus buat kalian kalau nonton teriak-teriak pasti haus, nah kalian harus minum pakai MoonStar Brew Tumbler!
And for you guys, if you watch and scream you'll surely get thirsty, so you must drink using the MoonStar Brew Tumbler!
Bintang akuarium!
Aquarium Star!
Yeah!
Dan selanjutnya, buat kalian nih, buat kalian yang suka sama voice-nya Moona, suka sama suaranya Moona...
And next, for those of you who like Moona's voice, who like Moona's singing voice...
Moona ada tiga situational voice yang berisi...
Moona has three situational voices containing...
Tiga bahasa! Uh!
Three languages! Uh!
Wah, kalau kalian membeli full setnya...
Wow, if you buy the full set...
Akan ada bonus postcard dengan ilustrasi dari Nyori-sensei, dan ditandatangani oleh Moona!
There will be a postcard bonus with an illustration by Nyori-sensei, and signed by Moona!
Cuma nya terbatas loh, jadi jangan sampai kehabisan!
The quantity is limited, so make sure you don't miss out!
Hah, kemudian nih, ini, waduh...
Ha, then this, this, wow...
Nggak bisa-bisa, guys! Sebagai bonus dari pembelian full set premium merch, akan ada tambahan bonus satu kartu yang bisa digunakan di...
It's impossible, guys! As a bonus for purchasing the full set of premium merch, there will be an extra bonus card that can be used in...
Hololive Official Card Game, yang dijual tahun lalu.
the Hololive Official Card Game, which was sold last year.
Nah, kartu ini hanya tersedia untuk pembelian di Official Shop Hololive Productions.
Now, this card is only available for purchase at the official Hololive Productions shop.
Bonus yang bisa didapat adalah kartu Oshi Holamem card, hm!
The bonus you can get is an Oshi Hololive Member card, hm!
Tapi kartunya hanya tersedia dalam bahasa Jepang, jadi mohon pengertiannya ya.
But the card is only available in Japanese, so please understand.
Hmm, untuk detail kartu dan cara bermain, silakan cek homepage-nya!
Hmm, for card details and how to play, please check the homepage!
Yeah, itulah...
Yeah, that's...
pengumuman untuk merch di birthday kali ini.
the announcement for the merch in this birthday.
Sehabis ini kita akan ada lagu lagi, teman-teman, yaitu Multiverse dan Nightmare!
After this, we'll have another song, friends, which is Multiverse and Nightmare!
Jadi, Moona mau ganti baju dulu ya! Bye-bye, see you later!
So, Moona is going to change clothes first! Bye-bye, see you later!
Cried about a thousand tears,
真夜中に彷徨うことは何度もあった
How many times did I wander in the middle of the night
I found myself in that place, saw the real me,
全てには意味があったのさ
Everything had a meaning
I've got a side to me that I haven't shown,
My every scar shows a different kind of glow,
飛び立つのか、そう、yeah, I'm moving on to a higher plane,
Time to take flight, yeah, I'm moving on to a higher plane,
あの日々は like a far away echo,
Those days are like a far away echo,
何回だって
No matter how many times
傷ついていいから
It's okay to get hurt
Never want to lose myself in the unknown,
偽りない旅へと
To a journey without falsehoods
All through my soul, let it burn,
広がる multiverse, 増えてく my universe, my universe now,
Expanding multiverse, growing my universe, my universe now,
美しく彩っていく my multiverse, I'll grow from the hurt,
Beautifying and coloring my multiverse, I'll grow from the hurt,
Hear it now, my destiny is calling,
光へ進む to saying softly,
Advancing toward the light, saying softly,
Even when I fall, gotta dust it off,
Even when I'm lost, gotta keep it up,
Step on it, step on it, bet everything like uh,
全てを手持ちで変えるの yeah this is my game,
Changing everything with my own hands yeah this is my game,
重力を追い風に このまま yeah I'm on my way,
Using gravity as a tailwind just like this yeah I'm on my way,
It's a lonely journey,
No one's here to save me no, I've got to go on 振り返らずに,
No one's here to save me no, I've got to go on without looking back,
All through my soul, let it burn,
広がる multiverse, 増えてく my universe, my universe now,
Expanding multiverse, growing my universe, my universe now,
暗闇の先には 輝く world, 捧げる ode to the hurt,
Beyond the darkness is a shining world, offering an ode to the hurt,
続いてく my universe, 迷い捨てて, 美しく彩っていく my multiverse,
Continuing my universe, leaving hesitation behind, beautifying my multiverse,
I'll grow from the hurt,
I'll grow from the dirt,
I'll grow from the pains of the days, burn,
I'll grow from the hurt,
I'll grow from the dirt,
I'll grow from the pains of the days when troubles come my way, that's when the stars are made,
Watch as my queendom rises higher, higher, in every darkest day it hides the sweetest taste,
Watch as my queendom rises higher, higher, all through my soul, let it burn,
広がる multiverse, 増えてく my universe, my universe now, 暗闇の先には 輝く world,
Expanding multiverse, growing my universe, my universe now, beyond the darkness is a shining world,
捧げる ode to the hurt, 続いてく my universe, 迷い捨てて, この軌跡に乗れば nothing's gonna stop me, 美しく彩っていく my multiverse, I'll grow from the hurt.
Offering an ode to the hurt, continuing my universe, leaving hesitation behind, riding on this orbit nothing's gonna stop me, beautifying and coloring my multiverse, I'll grow from the hurt.
my universe, my universe now
暗闇の先には 輝く world
Beyond the darkness is a shining world
捧げる ode to the hurt
Offering an ode to the hurt
続いてく my universe, 迷い捨てて
Continuing my universe, casting away doubts
美しく 彩っていく my multiverse
Beautifying and coloring my multiverse
i'll grow from the hurt
未知なる 感覚 痺れ て
Numb from an unknown sensation
聴こえる ノクターン
I hear a nocturne
感情 は 罠
Emotion is a trap
in the dark night, i won't cry
it's a show time
yeah nightmare
ram papa pampam, nightmare
ram papa pampam, crazy
歪む 空想 世界
A distorted fantasy world
目に沁み込む blackness
Blackness stinging the eyes
意味 も ない sympathy
Sympathy that has no meaning
oh no
閉ざして 落ちる fall in'
Closing in and falling down, fall in'
骨 まで 伝わる 衝動
Impulses running down to the bones
仮面 を つけ た evil
Evil wearing a mask
指差して 笑う 空想
Fantasies pointing and laughing
ここ まで が fantasy なんて
Saying it's only fantasy up to here
もう 呼吸 が 乱れ て
My breathing is already disordered
重たい 足 で
With heavy feet
今日 も 歩き出す
I start walking again today
in the night
理性的 な 制御
Rational control
“自惚れる な よ”
"Don't flatter yourself"
聴こえてくる nightmare
I can hear it coming, nightmare
ああ きっと 眠れ ない
Ah, surely I cannot sleep
砕け そう な 感傷
Sentiments on the verge of shattering
渦巻く 感情
Swirling emotions
手放せ たら な
If only I could let them go
浸る shadow
Immersed in shadow
yeah nightmare
ram papa pampam, nightmare
ram papa pampam, crazy
ぶつかり合う memory
Memories colliding with each other
本当に？ 私は 必要な い
Really? I am not needed
常識 と は telling lies
Common sense is telling lies
ずっと 答え の ない 闇
Darkness with no answer all along
消せ ない 間違い
Mistakes that cannot be erased
誤魔化す ほど に
The more I try to gloss over it
こぼれ落ちる 期待
Expectations spilling out
in the night
犠牲 的 な 正体
The true identity of sacrifice
欲 の 無い 希望
Hope without desires
失う まで nightmare
Until I lose everything, nightmare
ああ もっと 手を 伸ばす
Ah, reaching out my hands even more
続いていく 残像
Afterimages continuing on
振り解け ば 笑える の か な
If I shake them off, will I be able to smile?
足掻いて
Struggling
許さ れる？ don't know
Will I be forgiven? don't know
満たされ たい let go
I want to be fulfilled, let go
信じる 事 が できた なら
If I were able to believe
in the night
理性的 な 制御
Rational control
“自惚れる な よ”
"Don't flatter yourself"
聴こえてくる nightmare
I can hear it coming, nightmare
ああ きっと 眠れ ない
Ah, surely I cannot sleep
砕け そう な 感傷
Sentiments on the verge of shattering
渦巻く 感情
Swirling emotions
手放せ たら な
If only I could let them go
目覚める
Waking up
yeah nightmare
ram papa pampam, nightmare
ram papa pampam, crazy
MOONA HOSHINOVA "PANDORA"
Pre-orders open today at 22:00 JST / 20:00 WIB!
Available exclusively at hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP
Exciting announcements!
My first full album, Pandora, is officially happening! Yay!
This will be the first album from Hololive Indonesia.
The album includes four brand-new songs, including the collaboration track "100%" with Nerissa, which I just pre-performed today.
It also features previously released songs like "Mike Me" from last year, making a total of 10 tracks.
The CD comes in two editions: Limited Bonus Editions and Regular Editions.
Limited Bonus Editions include a CD jacket with my handwritten autographs. This is a one-of-a-kind autograph just for you!
Comes with an online Meet & Greet lottery application ticket, plus a special letter from Moona and two clear bookmarks.
It's a super deluxe package!
Regular editions come with one random trading card. There are four different types plus one secret type. Can't wait to see which one you get!
Pre-orders open right after this on the Hololive Production official shop. Make sure to grab your copy!
By the way, the digital album is set to release on April 12th, the day after my first ever livestreamed anniversary!
Thank you for all your incredible supports. I wouldn't be able to make music without you.
Moona Hoshinova, Pandora.
Hope you're as excited as I am.
Thank you for coming to my 3D Birthday ★
your love and support make everything shine even brighter !
Thank you for coming to my 3D Birthday!
Your love and support make everything shine even brighter!
it's been an incredible-almost 5 years together and
i can't wait to make even more amazing memories
It's been an incredible almost 5 years together, and
I can't wait to make even more amazing memories
with all of you !
~Love Moona 🌙
with all of you!
~ Love Moona 🌙